<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cool Movies</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string-array name="movies">
        <item>Coming 2 America</item>
        <item>Raya and the Last Dragon</item>
        <item>I Care a Lot</item>
        <item>Hereditary</item>
        <item>The Little Things</item>
        <item>Get Out</item>
        <item>Us</item>
        <item>Black Widow</item>
        <item>Joker</item>
        <item>Last Holiday</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="comming2america">
        "On the 30th anniversary of his wedding with Lisa McDowell, Prince Akeem of Zamunda is summoned before his dying father, King Jaffe Joffer. Jaffe and his shaman Baba reveal to a baffled Akeem that he had sired a son during his first visit in Queens, New York, after his aide Semmi had enticed two women into spending the night with them while Akeem was still searching for his future queen. One of them inadvertently drugged Akeem, resulting in a tryst he did not remember. As Zamundian tradition demands that only a male successor can inherit the throne, and Lisa has borne only daughters, Akeem is forced to travel back to Queens to retrieve his son. If not, Zamunda could face a hostile takeover by Zamunda's militaristic neighbor nation Nexdoria, whose dictator, General Izzi (the brother of Akeem's original arranged bride-to-be), has been pushing Akeem's eldest daughter Meeka into marrying his foppish son, Idi.
        Following King Jaffe's funeral and Akeem's ascension to king, he and Semmi travel to Queens to meet his illegitimate son, Lavelle Junson, who is a smart-mouthed ticket scalper struggling to get a real job. After an awkward reunion with his mother Mary, Akeem takes them and Lavelle's uncle Reem back to Zamunda, much to his family's displeasure. When General Izzi learns of this, he drops by to introduce his daughter Bopoto to Lavelle as a last shot at laying claim to the throne of Zamunda, but in order to qualify as a royal prince, Lavelle firstly has to pass a series of traditional - and hazardous - tests.
        Lavelle is at first highly reluctant to place himself in danger, but then bonds with Mirembe, a royal groomer, who tells him of Akeem's quest to find his queen and encourages him to follow his own path. Lavelle gradually develops an understanding with Akeem's family and, using his wits and some forced courage, he passes and is made Prince of Zamunda. However, at his accession party, Lavelle overhears a conversation between Akeem and Izzi which makes him believe that Akeem is just exploiting him, and he, Mirembe, Mary and Reem go back to New York. Upset at losing Mary, whom she has befriended, Lisa locks Akeem out of their bedroom. After talking with Cleo, who reminds him of late Queen Aoleon's progressive mind, Akeem flies back to the States, while Semmi is left to stall Izzi, who intends to return the next day to either see Bopoto marry Lavelle or declare war.
        Returning to Queens, Akeem finds that Lavelle and Mirembe are about to get married. Reminded of his own life story, he gives them his blessing and releases Lavelle from his marriage to Bopoto. In the meantime, Semmi and the princesses fight off and subdue General Izzi, forcing him to try a more diplomatic approach. Upon his return home, Akeem changes the royal succession by allowing his daughter Meeka to ascend to the throne upon his death, while Lavelle is made an ambassador of Zamunda to the United States and General Izzi has opened Nexdoria for a peaceful political and trading relationship. The film concludes with a grand party at the royal palace, including Akeem's barbershop friends from Queens as special guests and a performance of the song "We Are Family" from Sexual Chocolate."
    </string>
    <string name="raya">
        "Kumandra is a prosperous land rampaged by the Druun, evil spirits that petrify people and multiply after absorbing their life force. The dragons of Kumandra used their remaining magic to create an orb to ward off the Druun and revive everyone, but end up turning to stone themselves. A power struggle for the orb divides Kumandra's people into tribes, based on their placement along a giant river that resembles a dragon: Fang, Heart, Spine, Talon, and Tail.
        500 years later, Chief Benja of the Heart tribe has been training his daughter Raya to guard the orb while firmly believing that the tribes will be united once again. During a feast among the five tribes, Raya befriends the daughter of Chief Virana of the Fang tribe, Namaari, who gives Raya a dragon pendant as a gift. Trusting her, Raya shows Namaari the location of the orb, but Namaari has called members of her tribe who attempt to steal the orb. The other tribes arrive and fight for the orb, resulting in its breaking into five pieces. The Druun suddenly reappear as each of the tribes steal a piece, with Benja among the casualties.
        For the next six years, Raya attempts to find Sisu, a dragon said to have created the orb and the only surviving member of her species, to help her recover the missing orb pieces. While in the Tail Tribe's former territory, she finally manages to summon Sisu, who admits that she did not create the orb but can use its powers. They recover the second piece in a ruined Tail temple, granting Sisu shapeshifting powers. They have a hostile encounter with Namaari and her tribe, but young entrepreneur Boun, who had lost his family to the Druun, helps them escape. Despite Boun's friendliness, Raya does not fully trust him.
        They arrive at Talon to claim the third orb piece, during which Raya encounters "con baby" Little Noi and her trio of monkey-like companions, the Ongis, who adopted her after the Druun killed her mother. After a chase, Raya takes her in, while Sisu goes into town and encounters Talon's chieftess, who threatens her. Raya rescues Sisu and reclaims the third piece, which allows Sisu to spew out fog.
        The group arrives at Spine, where Raya and Sisu meet Tong, a fearsome warrior and the village's sole survivor. The rest of the group catches up to warn them of Namaari's arrival. Raya holds her off in a fight while the others escape, with Sisu assisting her. Back at the boat, Raya tells the truth about Sisu to her party and they agree to work together, with Tong handing Spine's orb piece to Sisu, giving her the power over rain.
        As they get closer to Fang, Sisu suggests asking for the final piece rather than stealing it. When Raya refuses, Sisu takes her back to the remains of the Heart and tells of how she was trusted by her siblings to save Kumandra. Raya relents and decides to give Namaari the dragon pendant as a peace offering to complete her quest. Raya and Sisu meet privately with Namaari, but upon seeing the orb pieces, Namaari threatens them. Sisu tries to talk her down, but gets unintentionally shot by Namaari and falls into a river, which begins to dry up.
        Fang is attacked by the Druun, as Raya enters to confront Namaari, who is mourning the loss of her mother. The two fight while Raya's companions rescue the people from the Druun. Raya prepares to kill Namaari, but after seeing her remorse, they run to help her friends instead. As the Druun advance toward Raya's group, Raya tells them that they need to reassemble the orb, but her friends refuse to forgive Namaari. To show her faith, Raya gives Namaari her piece and allows the Druun to take her. The rest follow suit, with Namaari fixing the orb before the Druun take her. With the orb reassembled, the Druun are vanquished and everyone is brought back to life, including Sisu and the other dragons.
        Everyone is now able to reunite with their lost loved ones, including Raya and her father. The dragons and the tribes gather at Heart to celebrate and join together to form Kumandra once again."
    </string>
    <string name="careAlot">
        "Marla Grayson is a Massachusetts scammer who makes a living by convincing the legal system to grant her guardianship over elders she pretends cannot take care of themselves. She places them in an assisted living facility, where they are sedated and lose contact with the outside world. She then sells off their homes and assets, pocketing the proceeds. She and the court deny a man, Mr. Feldstrom, access to his mother after he attempts to force his way in to the assisted living facility. He later threatens her outside the courthouse, saying that he hopes she is murdered.
        Dr. Karen Amos informs Marla about a wealthy retiree they can exploit, Jennifer Peterson. A judge appoints Marla guardian after she and Dr. Amos falsely testify that Jennifer suffers from dementia and confusion. Marla moves Jennifer into assisted living and immediately gets to work selling Jennifer's furniture, car and home. While rooting through Jennifer's possessions, Marla discovers the key to a safe deposit box containing a watch, gold bars, bank notes and hidden diamonds, which she takes and stashes away.
        As Marla's girlfriend and business partner, Fran, helps renovate the house, a man driving a cab arrives and claims that he is there to pick up Jennifer. Fran informs him that Jennifer has moved. He returns to his employer, Roman Lunyov, greatly distressed, who threatens him with a gun. Roman, a crime lord, is Jennifer's son. He orders his underling Alexi to investigate his mother's living situation. Mafia lawyer Dean Ericson offers to pay Marla $150,000 in cash to release Jennifer but she refuses. He threatens Marla and takes her to court. The judge dismisses the case as he cannot prove Jennifer hired him.
        Fran discovers "Jennifer Peterson" is an identity stolen from a girl who died of polio. When Jennifer refuses to tell Marla her real identity, Marla teams up with Property manager Sam Rice, having many of Jennifer’s basic needs withdrawn. Roman, finding his mother's safe deposit box rifled, sends three thugs to Jennifer's facility to take her. This violent effort fails and Marla helps police apprehend one of the men, Alexi. Fran's police contact informs them that Alexi is the sibling of two other mafia bosses who supposedly died in a fire. Having failed to rescue his mother, Roman has Dr. Amos killed at her office. After hearing the news, Marla and Fran move into one of the unsold properties belonging to one of Marla's previous victims. At the facility, Marla deliberately mocks and insults Jennifer, telling her she will die alone in a few years, and Jennifer, provoked, attacks Marla. Marla distorts the situation at court to convince Judge Lomax to move her to a psychiatric facility.
        Marla is kidnapped while Fran is attacked in their home. Marla is brought before Roman Lunyov, where she asks for $10 million for Jennifer's release. Roman is impressed by her audacity, but refuses her request. His associates knock her out with chloroform and send her in a car into a lake. She escapes and returns home to find Fran unconscious and badly bruised as gas fills the house. They narrowly escape an explosion and flee to another unsold property, where Marla shows Fran diamonds she has hidden there. She offers Fran a choice: they can use the diamonds to leave right away and start a new life elsewhere or they can get revenge.
        They track down Roman through his license plate number and kidnap him. They drug him, steal his car, take him into the wilderness, leave him nude on a trail, and burn his car. Roman is discovered by a jogger. Unable to establish his identity, a judge designates him a "John Doe" and appoints Marla as his legal guardian. Marla visits Roman and offers to release him and Jennifer from her guardianship for $10 million. Instead, Roman offers her a partnership in a global business based on her scam. She accepts and, using his money and connections, quickly becomes a powerful, extremely wealthy CEO. Roman is reunited with Jennifer, while Marla marries Fran.
        While leaving a TV interview about her success, Marla is shot by Mr. Feldstrom, who tearfully reports that his mother died alone in the assisted living facility because no one would let him see her. As Fran cries out for help and Mr. Feldstrom is arrested, Marla dies in her arms."
    </string>
    <string name="joker">
        "In 1981, party clown and aspiring stand-up comedian Arthur Fleck lives with his mother, Penny, in Gotham City. Gotham is rife with crime and unemployment, leaving swaths of the population disenfranchised and impoverished. Arthur suffers from a medical disorder that causes him to laugh at inappropriate times, depending on social services for medication. After a gang of delinquents attacks Arthur in an alley, his co-worker Randall gives him a gun for protection. Arthur pursues a relationship with his neighbor, single mother Sophie Dumond, and invites her to his upcoming stand-up routine at a nightclub.
        While entertaining at a children's hospital, Arthur's gun falls out of his pocket. Randall lies that Arthur bought the gun himself, and Arthur is fired. On the subway, still in his clown makeup, Arthur is beaten by three drunken Wayne Enterprises businessmen; he shoots two in self-defense and wounds the third before pursuing him off the train and executing him on the stairs. The killings are condemned by billionaire mayoral candidate Thomas Wayne, who calls those envious of more successful people "clowns." Demonstrations against Gotham's rich begin, with protesters donning clown masks in Arthur's image. Funding cuts shut down the social service program, leaving Arthur without his medication.
        Sophie attends Arthur's stand-up routine, which goes poorly; he laughs uncontrollably and has difficulty delivering his jokes. Arthur's idol, popular talk show host, Murray Franklin, mocks Arthur by showing clips from the comedy routine on his show. Arthur intercepts a letter written by Penny to Thomas, alleging that he is Thomas's illegitimate son, and berates his mother for hiding the truth. Arthur goes to Wayne Manor, where he meets Thomas's young son Bruce, but flees after a scuffle with the family butler Alfred Pennyworth. Following a visit from two Gotham City Police Department detectives investigating Arthur's involvement in the train murders, Penny suffers a stroke and is hospitalized.
        Arthur sneaks into a private viewing event presenting the Charlie Chaplin film Modern Times and confronts Thomas, who tells him that Penny is delusional and not his biological mother. In denial, Arthur visits Arkham State Hospital and steals Penny's case file; the file says Penny adopted Arthur as a baby and allowed her abusive boyfriend to harm them both. However, Penny claims that Thomas used his influence to fabricate the adoption to hide their affair. Distraught, Arthur returns home and enters Sophie's apartment unannounced. Frightened, Sophie tells him to leave; their relationship was merely a figment of Arthur's imagination. The following day, Arthur kills Penny at the hospital.
        Arthur is invited to appear on Murray's show due to the unexpected popularity of his comedy routine's clips. As he prepares, Arthur is visited by ex-colleagues Randall and Gary. Arthur murders Randall but spares Gary for treating him well in the past. En route to the studio, Arthur is pursued by the two detectives onto a train filled with clown protesters. One detective accidentally shoots a protester and incites a riot, allowing Arthur to escape; the rioters brutally beat the detectives as Arthur leaves.
        Before the show goes live, Arthur requests that Murray introduce him as Joker, a reference to Murray's previous mockery. Arthur walks out to applause, but starts telling morbid jokes, confesses to the train murders, rants about how society abandons the downtrodden and mentally ill, and berates Murray for mocking him on the previous segment. When Murray criticizes him and threatens to call the police, Arthur shoots him twice on live television, killing him; he is arrested for murder as riots break out across Gotham. One of the rioters corners the Wayne family in an alley and murders Thomas and his wife, Martha, sparing Bruce.[a] Rioters in an ambulance crash into the police car carrying Arthur, freeing him; he stands atop the car, dances to the cheers of the crowd, and smears blood on his face in the form of a smile.
        At Arkham, Arthur laughs to himself about a joke and tells his psychiatrist she would not understand it. He runs from an orderly, leaving behind a trail of bloodied footprints."
    </string>
    <string name="littleThings">
        "One night in 1990, a girl drives on a highway, stalked by a motorist. She pulls over at a gas station, where the motorist follows her. The gas station is closed and she is forced to run through the desert. She catches the attention of a passing truck driver, escaping from the pursuit.
        Some time later in Bakersfield, Kern County deputy sheriff Joe "Deke" Deacon is called to the Los Angeles County Sheriff's Department to collect evidence pertaining to a recent murder. Deacon, a former L.A. Sheriff's detective, accompanies recently appointed lead detective Jimmy Baxter to the scene of a new murder in L.A. Deacon notices similarities between the M.O. of the killing and the M.O. of an old serial murder case he was unable to solve.
        That night, a woman, named Ronda Rathbun, is followed by a car while jogging and is reported missing the following morning. Baxter learns from the precinct's captain, Farris, that Deacon got divorced and suffered a heart attack due to his obsession with the unsolved case. He's advised not to involve him any further but Deacon takes vacation leave to assist in solving Baxter's case.
        The next night, the police discover the body of another victim washed up beneath a bridge. Baxter learns the M.O. is consistent with the earlier murder and earlier killings: the victims were all prostitutes stabbed to death. Deacon begins investigating Albert Sparma, a suspect working at a repair store in proximity to the murders. Deacon tails Sparma, but is thwarted, so he brings Sparma in for questioning. Sparma taunts the detectives while under interrogation, and is released after provoking Deacon into an angry outburst.
        The FBI is called in to take charge of the investigation within the week, giving Deacon and Baxter less time. Farris informs Baxter that eight years prior, Sparma confessed to a murder which he couldn't have committed since he was ten miles away from it at the time. Also that he's obsessed with crime and is thus an unreliable suspect. Baxter and Deacon go to Sparma’s apartment and conduct an illegal search. As Deacon searches the apartment, a police radio goes off and he escapes from Sparma’s home after Sparma called in an “officer down”. Police arrive and Deacon escapes while Baxter sees Sparma watching the ordeal. After an unsuccessful search of Sparma's apartment the two detectives tail Sparma to a strip club the following night. Baxter corners Sparma alone and demands to know Rathbun's location. Sparma offers to drive him to where he supposedly hid Rathbun's body, and Baxter cautiously agrees while Deacon follows.
        Sparma takes Baxter to a remote area in the desert and has him dig several holes before admitting that he never killed anyone. Baxter is skeptical, and continues digging. Sparma begins to taunt him, until Baxter snaps and strikes him in the face with a shovel, killing him. As Deacon arrives, a flashback reveals that he accidentally shot one of the survivors of his last murder case, and that Farris and Dunigan, the coroner, helped cover it up. Deacon instructs Baxter to bury Sparma in the desert. Deacon spends the night collecting everything in Sparma's apartment and returns to the desert the following morning to find that Baxter has not buried Sparma and is still searching for the victim. Baxter is desperate to believe Sparma is the killer, hoping it will clear his conscience and close the case. Deacon advises him to forget about the case or it will haunt him for life.
        Later, at his home, Baxter receives an envelope sent by Deacon, containing a red barrette like the one Ronda Rathbun was wearing when she was abducted. Back in Kern County, Deacon burns everything he collected in the apartment, along with a brand new three-pack of barrettes that’s missing a red barrette."
    </string>
    <string name="hereditary">
        "Artist Annie Graham lives in Utah with her husband Steve, their 16-year-old son Peter, and their eccentric and reserved daughter Charlie. At the funeral of her secretive mother, Ellen Leigh, Annie delivers a eulogy explaining their fraught relationship and her mother's extremely private life. A week later, Steve is informed that Ellen's grave has been desecrated, and Annie thinks she sees an apparition of Ellen in her workshop. At a support group for the bereaved, Annie reveals that the rest of her family suffered from mental illness that resulted in their deaths and Ellen was a significant figure in raising Charlie.
        To attend a party, Peter lies that he is going to a school event, and Annie forces him to take Charlie with him. Unsupervised, Charlie eats cake containing nuts and falls into anaphylactic shock. As Peter drives her to a hospital, she leans out of the window for air; when he swerves to avoid a dead deer, she is decapitated by a telephone pole. In shock, Peter drives home and leaves Charlie's headless corpse in the car. The family grieves following Charlie's funeral, heightening tensions between Annie and Peter and causing Annie to behave coldly towards Steve. Peter is plagued by Charlie's presence around the house.
        Annie is befriended by a support-group member, Joan. Annie tells her she used to sleepwalk and recounts an incident in which she woke up in Peter's bedroom to find herself, Peter, and Charlie covered in paint thinner with a lit match in her hand. Joan teaches Annie to perform a séance to communicate with Charlie. Annie convinces her family to attempt the séance. Objects begin to move and break, terrifying Peter, and Charlie seemingly possesses Annie until Steve douses her with water. Annie suspects that Charlie's spirit has become malevolent. She throws Charlie's sketchbook into the fireplace but her sleeve also begins to burn. She retrieves it and heads to Joan's apartment for advice, but Joan is gone. Annie notices that Joan's welcome mat resembles her mother's craftwork. It is also revealed that rituals inside the apartment involve pictures of Peter.
        Annie goes through her mother's possessions and finds a photo album linking Joan to Ellen, and a book with information about a demon named Paimon who wishes to inhabit the body of a male host. In the attic, Annie finds Ellen's decapitated body with occult symbols on the wall written in blood. At school, Peter slams his head against his desk, breaking his nose, and is brought home. Annie shows Steve her mother's body and the sketchbook. She begs him to burn the sketchbook so she can sacrifice herself to stop the haunting, but he thinks she has gone mad and accuses her of desecrating Ellen's grave herself. Annie throws the book into the fireplace, which makes Steve suddenly burst into flames. As Annie screams in terror, Paimon takes possession of her, and she immediately falls silent and into a trance.
        Outside, a coven of worshippers begins to assemble. Peter awakens to find his father's body before a possessed Annie chases him into the attic, which is decorated with occult imagery. Despite Peter locking himself inside, he suddenly discovers Annie in the attic, levitating in the air looking down on him while beheading herself with a piano wire while naked coven members watch Peter with eerie smiles. Terrified, Peter jumps out of the window. As he lies on the ground, a shadow is seen passing over his body, whereafter a light enters it in its place and he wakes up. He follows Annie's levitating corpse into Charlie's treehouse, where Charlie's crowned, severed head rests atop a mannequin. Joan, other coven members, and the headless corpses of his mother and grandmother bow to him. Joan addresses him as Charlie and swears an oath to him, informing him that he is Paimon, one of the eight kings of hell, and that he has now been liberated from his female host. She asks him to "bind all men to their will as they have bound theirs now and for ever to his."
    </string>
    <string name="getOut">
        "Black photographer Chris Washington is apprehensive as he prepares to meet the family of his white girlfriend, Rose Armitage. Later, at the Armitage house in rural Upstate New York, Rose's brother Jeremy and their parents, neurosurgeon Dean and hypnotherapist Missy, make disconcerting comments about black people. Chris witnesses strange behavior from the estate's black housekeeper Georgina and groundskeeper Walter. When Chris is unable to sleep, Missy pressures him into a hypnotherapy session to cure his smoking addiction. In a trance, he expresses guilt over his mother's death in a hit-and-run when he was a child, and sinks into a void Missy calls the "Sunken Place". The next morning, he assumes that the encounter was a dream until Walter acknowledges their brief encounter the night before.
        Dozens of wealthy white people arrive for the Armitages' annual get-together. They express admiration for Chris's physique and for black figures such as Tiger Woods. Jim Hudson, a blind art dealer, takes a particular interest in Chris's photography skills. Chris meets another black man, Logan King, who behaves strangely and is married to a much older white woman. Chris calls his friend, TSA officer Rod Williams, about the strange behavior. Chris tries to photograph Logan inconspicuously, but when his flash goes off, Logan becomes hysterical, shouting at Chris to "get out". The others restrain him and Dean claims that Logan had a seizure. Away from the party, Chris convinces Rose that they should leave. Meanwhile, Dean holds an auction with a photo of Chris, which Hudson wins. Rod recognizes "Logan" as Andre Hayworth, a missing man. Suspecting a conspiracy, Rod goes to the police, but no one believes him. While Chris packs to leave, he finds photos of Rose in prior relationships with black people, including Walter and Georgina, contradicting her claim that Chris is her first black boyfriend. He tries to leave the house, but Rose and her family block him. Chris attacks Jeremy, but Missy uses a "trigger" that she implanted during his hypnosis, knocking him out.
        Chris awakens strapped to a chair in the basement. In a video presentation, Rose's grandfather Roman explains that the family transplants their brains into others' bodies, granting them preferred physical characteristics and a twisted form of immortality. Hudson tells Chris the host's consciousness remains in the Sunken Place, conscious but powerless. Although the Armitages target mainly black people, Hudson reveals he wants Chris's body only for sight and his photography skills. Missy performs hypnosis, seemingly knocking Chris out. When Jeremy comes to fetch Chris for the surgery, Chris bludgeons him unconscious, having blocked the hypnosis by plugging his ears with cotton stuffing pulled from the chair. He impales Dean with the antlers of a deer mount, causing Dean to knock over a candle, setting fire to the operating room with Hudson inside. Chris kills Missy but is attacked by Jeremy as he heads towards the door; he overpowers and kills Jeremy before leaving in his car, but hits Georgina. Remembering his mother's death, he carries Georgina into the car. However, possessed by Rose's grandmother Marianne, she attacks him. During the struggle the car crashes, killing both Georgina and Marianne.
        Rose confronts him with a rifle, aided by Walter, who is possessed by Roman. Chris uses the flash on his phone to neutralize Roman, allowing Walter to regain control of his body. Walter takes Rose's rifle, shoots her in the stomach, and shoots himself, killing both him and Roman. Chris begins to strangle Rose, but cannot bring himself to follow through and stops. A police cruiser pulls onto the scene, where Rose cries for help. Rod then steps out of the "TSA" cruiser and rescues Chris, leaving Rose bleeding out on the road."
    </string>
    <string name="blackWidow">
        "A film about Natasha Romanoff in her quests between the films Civil War and Infinity War.
        As expected, Scarlett Johansson is set to return as Black Widow to star in the film. A first look at the movie came through a poster shared on Instagram by Marvel concept artist Andy Park showed that Black Widow is set to feature classic Marvel villain Taskmaster.
        At birth the Black Widow "aka Natasha Romanova" is given to the KGB, which grooms her to become its ultimate operative. When the U.S.S.R. breaks up, the government tries to kill her as the action moves to present-day New York, where she is a freelance operative.
    In Marvel Studios' action-packed spy thriller "Black Widow," Natasha Romanoff aka Black Widow confronts the darker parts of her ledger when a dangerous conspiracy with ties to her past arises. Pursued by a force that will stop at nothing to bring her down, Natasha must deal with her history as a spy and the broken relationships left in her wake long before she became an Avenger."
    </string>
    <string name="lastHoliday">
        "The film begins during the Christmas holiday season with Georgia Byrd, an employee in the cookware department at Kragen's Department Store in New Orleans. Georgia is a shy, unassuming woman who longs to cook professionally, and who records her dreams of a better life in a scrapbook labeled "Possibilities". While flirting with a co-worker named Sean Williams, Georgia bumps her head on a kitchen cabinet door and is taken to the store's health center for a CAT scan. There, she is told by company physician Dr. Gupta that she has several brain tumors resulting from a rare neurological disorder called Lampington's disease. Since her HMO plan will not cover the exorbitant cost of an operation, Georgia resigns herself to the fact she has only a few weeks to live, quits her job, liquidates her assets and sets off on a dream vacation at the deluxe Grandhotel Pupp in the spa city of Karlovy Vary in the Czech Republic.
        Free of inhibitions and determined to live life to the fullest, Georgia checks into the Presidential Suite, buys a designer wardrobe in expensive boutiques, makes extensive use of the hotel's spa facilities, attempts snowboarding and BASE jumping off a dam, enjoys succulent meals prepared by world-renowned Chef Didier, and wins a small fortune playing roulette in the casino.
        Georgia impresses the hotel's staff, with the exception of cantankerous guest services manager Miss Gunther, with her naive manner and forthright kindness, and mingles with some of the other guests, including Matthew Kragen, a self-help guru and coincidentally the owner of the store where she worked; his assistant/mistress Ms. Allison Burns; pandering Senator Dillings from her home state of Louisiana; and prominent Congressman Stewart. Kragen is skeptical about Georgia's origins and suspects her of trying to sabotage his business, but the rest are charmed by her free spirit.
        Georgia returns to the hotel, and Sean leaves his taxi behind and begins to hike across the snow on foot. At a New Year's Eve party that evening, Kragen exposes Georgia as a low-level saleswoman in one of his stores. Georgia tells them that Kragen is right and reveals that she is going to die. Kragen's colleagues, disgusted by his insensitivity, embrace her and abandon him. Allison Burns leaves him, saying that she will return to school, and get her business degree; adding that she will be all to happy to help Kragen's wife divorce him and figure out exactly how much half of his fortune will be. Dejected and embarrassed, Kragen goes to an upper floor of the hotel and sits on the ledge, contemplating ending his life. Georgia tries to persuade him to come down, suggesting if he were nicer and less driven and greedy, he would be a happier person.
        Sean arrives at the hotel just in time and joins Georgia and Kragen on the ledge. In the lobby, Miss Gunther finds a fax from Dr. Gupta, in which he tells Georgia she was misdiagnosed due to X-rays generated by a broken, outdated CAT scanner. Miss Gunther rushes up to the ledge to announce the good news. Georgia and Sean return to New Orleans where they open a restaurant, which is visited by Chef Didier and Georgia's long-time inspiration: Emeril Lagasse."
    </string>
    <string name="us">
        "In 1986, a young girl, Adelaide Thomas, watches a commercial for Hands Across America. At night, at the Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk, she wanders off from her parents and enters a funhouse, where she encounters an identical doppelgänger of herself in the house of mirrors.
        Years later, now-adult Adelaide goes on vacation with her husband, Gabe Wilson, and their children, Zora and Jason. She is apprehensive about the trip, haunted by memories of the encounter and her recovery, during which she stopped speaking and withdrew from her family. Despite her misgivings, the family meet with their friends Josh and Kitty Tyler and their twin daughters at the beach. On the way there, they witness paramedics taking away the bloody body of an old man. Jason later sees someone strangely similar to the old man, standing still with his arms outstretched and hands bloody.
        That night, a family of four dressed in red appears in the driveway before breaking into the house. Cornering the Wilsons in their living room, they are revealed as the Wilsons' doppelgängers. They include Pluto (Jason's fire-loving, scarred double), Umbrae (Zora's sadistic double), and Abraham (Gabe's double), and are led by Red, Adelaide's double, the only one who can speak, albeit in a guttural, raspy voice. Red explains that they are called the "Tethered", they share a soul with their counterparts, and they have come to "untether" themselves. She tells them the story of a girl who lives a life of comfort and joy while her "shadow" remains in the dark, suffering while living a mirrored, painful version of the girl's life and hating the girl for it. The Wilsons are separated and terrorized by their doppelgängers. Adelaide is handcuffed and Jason discovers that Pluto mirrors his actions. After Gabe manages to kill Abraham, the Wilsons are able escape on their boat together.
        Meanwhile, the Tyler family are suddenly ambushed and murdered by their Tethered in their home. The Wilsons arrive and are attacked as well, but they manage to eventually overpower and kill the Tylers' doubles. Realizing they are not the only people with doppelgängers, they turn on the news to see that the Tethered have been murdering their equivalents across the U.S., and after doing so, joining hands to form a massive human chain. The Wilsons decide to drive along the coast and escape to Mexico. While leaving, Umbrae attacks the car; Zora kills her by sending her flying into a tree and breaking her back.
        Arriving at the boardwalk, the Wilsons find the townspeople have already been slaughtered. They also find the road blocked by a burning car, then realize it is a trap set by Pluto. Before Pluto can ignite the family's car, Jason backs away so that Pluto mirrors him and walks into the burning car. As Pluto dies, Red suddenly appears and snatches Jason. While Gabe recuperates from his wounds with Zora in an ambulance, Adelaide chases Red to the funhouse where they first met. She finds a secret entrance that leads to an underground facility overrun by rabbits, where she finds Red.
        Red explains that the Tethered are clones created by the government to control their counterparts on the surface. When the experiment failed, the Tethered were abandoned underground for generations, mindlessly mimicking the actions of their counterparts and surviving on rabbit meat. It was after they realized Red was "different" that she organized them to escape and take revenge by murdering their counterparts. Red and Adelaide fight, with Red evading and countering all of Adelaide's increasingly unbalanced attacks. When Adelaide allows Red to attack, she impales Red with a fireplace poker, then strangles her to death and breaks her neck, before rescuing Jason from a locker.
        While Adelaide drives the family away in the ambulance, she recalls the night she first met Red in the hall of mirrors. The doppelgänger choked Adelaide unconscious (damaging her larynx), dragged her underground, handcuffed her there, and returned above ground to take Adelaide's place, eventually learning to speak and adjusting; adult Red was actually the original Adelaide, who never forgot what was taken from her. Jason looks suspiciously at his mother, who merely gives him a sly smile. Across the hills of the U.S., the Tethereds' human chain, replicating the demonstration of Hands Across America, stretches for miles as news helicopters fly overhead."
    </string>
</resources>